Freeddy, Djiotsop Djiogue, Born on July 20th, 1994, Student

I like to program and use software to impact the world around me by software design and product development.

From my work experience, although that is not IT related, I'm experienced with Industry and customer requirements and I carry out my tasks to maximum satisfaction. This is my goal and drive in my professional life and personally.





CONTACT DETAILS

- djiotsopfreeddy@gmail.com
- **4** +49 176 42065141
- Schulstr. 3A, 41065 M'gladbach
- freeddy-djiotsop.de
- @Freeddy-Djiotsop

SKILLS

Programming

C/C++ HTML5/CSS3 Java/C#/Python **Javascript SQL**

Tools

MS Word LaTeX **MS Powerpoint MS Excel**

Operating Systems

Windows Linux Mac OS

Algorithms **Data Structure**

Exhaustive Search List **Backtracking** Qeue Greedy Stack **Divide and Conquer AVL-Tree Dynamic Programming** Heap

Hobbies

SW-Development Books Family Music Sport **Travel**

EDUCATION

Since April 2017

♀ University of Wuppertal

Bachelor of Sciences in InformatiK

March 2017

♀ Wuppertal

Obtaining the DSH 2

September 2016- Februar 2017

♀ Dortmund Germany

German courses B2-C1 at Perfekt Deutsch.

April 2016

Yaounde Cameroon

Obtaining the B1 Zertifikat

at Göthe Institut in Yaounde.

September 2014 - July 2016

♀ Douala Cameroon

German courses

A1-B1 at Deutsches Sprachenzentrum.

August 2014

Q Douala Cameroon

Scientific Baccalaureate D

September 1998 - June 2014

♀ Douala Cameroon

Primary and Secondary

Studies

WORK EXPERIENCE OUT OF IT

Since July 2020

♀ Mönchengladbach

May 2017 - December 2019

♀ Wuppertal

Februar 2018 - May 2019

Düsseldorf

Mc Donalds

Deutsche Post DHL Group

Foodora

LINKS

freeddy-djiotsop.de

@Freeddy-Djiotsop